?Are you ready, kids-
？你们准​​备好了吗，孩子们——
.KIDS: Aye aye, Captain
.KIDS：是啊，队长
.I can't hear you-
.我听不到你说话-
!KIDS: Aye aye, Captain
!KIDS：是啊，队长
SINGING) Oh, who lives in)-
.a pineapple under the sea
唱歌）哦，谁住在）-
.海底的菠萝
!KIDS: Spongebob Squarepants
!KIDS：海绵宝宝
CAPTAIN: Absorbent and
.yellow and porous is he
船长：吸水性和
.黄色多孔的是他
!KIDS: Spongebob Squarepants
!KIDS：海绵宝宝
CAPTAIN: If nautical nonsense
.be something you wish
船长：如果是航海方面的废话
.成为你想要的东西
!KIDS: Spongebob Squarepants
!KIDS：海绵宝宝
CAPTAIN: Then drop on the
.deck and glub like a fish
船长：然后降落在
.deck 和 glub 像鱼一样
!KIDS: Spongebob Squarepants
!KIDS：海绵宝宝
?CAPTAIN: Ready
?队长：准备好了
!ALL: Spongebob Squarepants
!ALL：海绵宝宝
!Spongebob Squarepants
!海绵宝宝
!CAPTAIN: Spongebob Squarepants
!CAPTAIN: 海绵宝宝
.NARRATOR: Ah
.旁白：啊
Sandy Cheeks is
going out of town
桑迪脸颊是
出城
and has asked
Spongebob and Patrick
并已询问
海绵宝宝和帕特里克
to do a little
.pet-sitting for her
做一点
.为她照顾宠物
?Pet-sitting-
?宠物看护-
?Won't that hurt them
？这不会伤害他们吗
NARRATOR: Perhaps she should
.have asked someone else
旁白：也许她应该
.已经问过别人了
[WHISTLING]
[口哨声]
.Gee, Patrick-
.哎呀，帕特里克-
.I didn't know you spoke bird
.我不知道你会说鸟语
.No, that's Italian, Spongebob-
.不，那是意大利语，海绵宝宝-
.OK, boys-
.好吧，孩子们-
.This here's Birdy's food
.这是Birdy的食物
.Feed him twice a day
.每天喂他两次
?This whole sack-
？整个麻袋-
.Naw, just a cup's worth-
.不，只是一杯的价值-
.This here's my cricket
.这是我的板球
.He's saying hello to you
.他在跟你打招呼
?Ain't he cute
？他不是很可爱吗
.Sorry, I don't speak Italian-
.抱歉，我不会说意大利语-
.OK-
。好的-
.And this here's snaky
.这很蛇
?What's that lump in his belly-
？他肚子里的那个肿块是什么-
.Well, that's his dinner-
.好吧，那是他的晚餐-
.Well, I guess that's it
.好吧，我想就是这样
.I gotta go
.我得走了
I'll see you fellers
.in a couple of days
我会见到你们这些家伙
.几天后
!BOTH: Bye, Sandy
！两者：再见，桑迪
!Wait-
！等待-
.You forgot about this pet
.你忘记了这只宠物
.Oh, that's only wormy-
.哦，那只是蠕虫-
.He don't eat much
.他吃得不多
.Look at him, Patrick-
.看看他，帕特里克-
?Isn't he great
？他不是很棒吗
!Hey, little fella
！嘿，小家伙
!Gitchy-gitchy goo-goo-
!Aw, look-
！噢，看——
?Isn't he just precious
？他不是很珍贵吗？
.Let's take him out to play
.我们带他出去玩吧
!998, 999, 1,000
!998、999、1,000
!Ready or not, here I come
！无论你准备好没，我来了
.You found me-
.你找到了我-
!BOTH: There you are
!BOTH：你来了
!D'oh
！噢
!He found us
！他找到了我们
SONG: A friend is
a friend to the end
歌曲： 一个朋友是
朋友到最后
of the end, that's
.forever and a day
的最后，那就是
.永远和一天
.Stay by your side
.留在你身边
Don't hear me say
,goodbye come what may
别听我说
无论如何，再见
.because that's what friends do
.因为这就是朋友所做的
.'Cause that's what friends do
Gee, Spongebob, I don't-
.want today to end ever
哎呀，海绵宝宝，我不-
.希望今天永远结束
.I know, Patrick-
.我知道，帕特里克-
,Days like today come once
.maybe twice in a lifetime
,像今天这样的日子会来一次
.也许一生两次
.Savour every moment
.品味每一刻
.And it's all thanks to Wormy
.这一切都归功于Wormy
,I made this for Wormy
.our new best friend
，这是我为蠕虫做的
.我们的新最好的朋友
.Until tomorrow, new best friend
.直到明天，新的最好的朋友
.Don't be sad, little buddy
.别伤心，小伙伴
We'll be back first thing in
.the morning for frolic and fun
我们会第一时间回来
.早上嬉戏和玩耍
Why must the sun set-
?on this perfect day
为什么太阳一定要落山——
？在这个完美的一天
.Sleep well, Wormy
.睡个好觉，蠕虫
[SOBBING]
[抽泣]
.Aw, don't be sad, Patrick-
.噢，别伤心，帕特里克-
.It's only until tomorrow
.只到明天
[CRICKETS]
[蟋蟀]
[ROOSTER]
[公鸡]
!Here I come, Wormy-
！我来了，蠕虫-
!Me too-
！我也是-
.And then we're gonna play tag
.然后我们要玩捉迷藏
.And then we're gonna colour
.然后我们要上色
And then we're gonna
.build a house of cards
然后我们要
.建造一座纸牌屋
!BOTH: We're back, Wormy
!BOTH：我们回来了，Wormy
!Wormy
！蠕虫
?Wormy-- where's Wormy-
？蠕虫--蠕虫在哪里-
?What's that thing
？那是什么东西
.He's got to be in here-
.他一定在这儿-
I think something bad
.happened to Wormy
我觉得有什么不好的
.发生在蠕虫身上
He left his Best-
.Friend ribbon behind
他留下了最好的——
.朋友丝带背后
[SCREAMING]
[尖叫]
?What is that thing-
？那是什么东西-
.I don't know, Patrick-
.我不知道，帕特里克-
But whatever it is, it
!must have eaten Wormy
但无论它是什么
！一定是吃虫子了
Why does this keep-
?happening to me
为什么这会一直——
？发生在我身上
.Quick, Patrick-
.快点，帕特里克-
We gotta make a
.run for the door
我们必须做一个
.跑向门口
!No
！不
.He's blocking our only exit
.他挡住了我们唯一的出口
?Now what-
？现在怎么办-
We're trapped in here with
!that-- that best friend eater
我们被困在这里
！那个——那个最好的朋友吃者
.Let's not panic-
.我们不要惊慌-
.We just have to stick together
.我们只需要团结在一起
.Remember, it's two against one
.记住，这是二对一
?Right, Patrick
？对吧，帕特里克
?Patrick
？帕特里克
!SCREAM] He's eaten Patrick]
！尖叫]他吃了帕特里克]
!Patrick, you're alive
！帕特里克，你还活着
?I am-
？我是-
Patrick, we can't just-
leave this horrible monster
帕特里克，我们不能只是-
离开这个可怕的怪物
.in Sandy's house
.在桑迪的家里
.It might eat Sandy's other pets
.它可能会吃桑迪的其他宠物
Or worse, it might-
.eat Sandy's pets
或者更糟糕的是，它可能——
.吃桑迪的宠物
.No, it might eat Sandy-
.不，它可能会吃桑迪-
.We gotta get it out of here
.我们得把它带出这里
[RINGING]
[铃声]
!It's for you-
！这是给你的——
.It's working-
.它正在工作-
!He's gonna answer it
！他会回答的
.Tartar sauce-
.塔塔酱-
You look pretty-
.appetising, Patrick
你看起来很漂亮-
.令人胃口大开，帕特里克
Now just stay here and
.wait for the monster
现在就呆在这里
.等待怪物
.I'll go get the net
.我去拿网
Spongebob, hurry-
!up with that net
海绵宝宝，快点——
！用那个网
.Hold on, Patrick-
.等等，帕特里克-
I really don't taste-
.that good, Mr. Monster
实在是没胃口——
.太好了，怪物先生
!I'm coming, Patrick-
！我来了，帕特里克-
.No, Mr. Monster
.不，怪物先生
!Please don't eat me
！请不要吃我
!No, no, no
！不，不，不
!Spare me
！饶了我吧
!I don't taste good
！我的味道不太好
!No, please
！不，请
.Wait a second
.等一下
!Yeah
！是的
!We did it, Patrick
！我们做到了，帕特里克
.Sandy's gonna be so proud of us
.桑迪会为我们感到骄傲
We got that horrible
.monster out of her house
我们得到了那可怕的
.怪物离开她的房子
,And best of all
,her pets are safe
，最重要的是
,她的宠物很安全
because that horrible
--creature is now
因为那太可怕了
——现在的生物
headed straight for
!the Krusty Krab
直奔
!蟹堡王
!It's going in the front
！它在前面
.Let's use the secret entrance
.让我们使用秘密入口吧
[GASP]
[喘气]
.OK, hold still-
.好吧，保持不动-
It's gonna eat-
!Squidward and Mr. Krabs
它会吃——
!章鱼哥和蟹老板
!Hit the deck, Mr. Krabs-
！上甲板吧，螃蟹先生-
.Say money-
.说钱-
.Money-
。钱-
What's the meaning-
?of this, Spongebob
有什么意义-
？这个，海绵宝宝
.We're in serious danger-
.我们正处于严重危险之中-
--There's a-- a-- a
.a monster out there
--有一个--一个--一个
.那里有一个怪物
?Is he a paying customer-
？他是付费客户吗-
.Oh no, Mr. Krabs-
.哦不，蟹老板-
It doesn't want to
.eat crabby patties
它不想
.吃螃蟹肉饼
!It wants to eat you
！它想吃掉你
.Just like it ate wormy-
.就像它吃了虫一样-
?Uh, wormy-
？呃，蠕虫-
[SOBBING]
[抽泣]
?BOTH: Oh, why
？两者：哦，为什么
?Why
？为什么
!So young-
！这么年轻——
!We'll never forget you, Wormy-
！我们永远不会忘记你，Wormy-
Well, if Moron-
Theatre is over, I
好吧，如果白痴——
剧场结束了，我
think I'll just take a
.look at this monster
我想我就拿一个
.看看这个怪物
?That's the monster
？这就是怪物
?Pretty scary, huh-
？相当可怕，嗯-
.A living nightmare-
.活生生的噩梦-
.I should have known-
.我应该知道-
.Well, that's it
.嗯，就是这样
I'm getting off
.the loony express
我要下车了
.疯狂快车
Now, just because you-
swabs never seen a creature
现在，只因为你——
拭子从未见过生物
like this doesn't
.mean it's dangerous
就像这样不
.意味着这很危险
.We tried to warn them-
.我们试图警告他们-
!I can't watch
！我看不了
Get a load of-
.the scary monster
获得负载-
.可怕的怪物
!Ha
！哈
.Monster
。怪物
!Ha
！哈
.Oh, it looks harmless-
.哦，它看起来无害-
.It's kinda cute-
.有点可爱-
.It reminds me of money-
.它让我想起了金钱-
.Monster-
。怪物-
!Ha ha
！哈哈
[SCREAMING]
[尖叫]
?Squidward-
？章鱼哥-
?Mr. Krabs-
？先生。蟹蟹-
!It ate them-
！它吃了它们——
!And there it goes
！就这样
First Wormy, then
!Squidward, Mr. Krabs
先是蠕虫，然后是
！章鱼哥，蟹老板
That flying monster has
!eaten three friends too many
那个会飞的怪物有
！三个朋友吃太多了
.We must inform the citizens
.我们必须告知公民
.Evil has surfaced
.邪恶已经浮现
The fate of Bikini Bottom
.is in our hands, Patrick
比基尼泳裤的命运
.在我们手中，帕特里克
.Now, let's roll
.现在，让我们开始吧
.Aye aye, Captain-
.是啊，船长-
.OK, Patrick-
.好吧，帕特里克-
This is a very
delicate situation
这是一个非常
局势微妙
and must be treated with
.great care and sensitivity
并且必须接受治疗
.非常细心和敏感
.Gotcha-
.明白了-
!Run-
！跑步-
!Everybody run
！大家跑
!Monster
！怪物
[SCREAMING]
[尖叫]
.Attention, Bikini Bottom-
.注意，比基尼泳裤-
There's a flying monster
.that's going to eat you
有一个会飞的怪物
.那会吃了你
[GASP]
[喘气]
:(REPORTER (ON TV
.Attention, attention
:(记者（电视上
.注意，注意
This just in, a giant monster
.is attacking Bikini Bottom
这刚刚进来，一个巨大的怪物
.正在攻击比基尼底部
!We did it, Patrick-
！我们做到了，帕特里克-
.We saved the city
.我们拯救了这座城市
Just think what might
have happened if we didn't
想想可能会发生什么
如果我们不这样做的话就会发生
.tell everyone about the monster
.告诉大家关于怪物的事
?About the what-
？关于什么-
!Shoot-
！射击-
Looks like a twister
.hit this place
看起来像个扭蛋
.击中这个地方
?Where is everybody
?大家都在哪里
!Aw, hi there, Wormy
！噢，你好，沃米
You weren't supposed to
.change till I got back
你不应该这样做
.改变直到我回来
That ought to hold
.you, little guy
这应该成立
.你，小家伙
[CHEERING]
[欢呼]
!Howdy, Spongebob
！你好，海绵宝宝
!Sandy caught the monster-
！桑迪抓住了怪物——
I didn't know I'd-
!be missed so much
我不知道我会-
！非常想念
!Golly
！发誓
Maybe I should go out
.of town more often
也许我应该出去
. 经常去城里
!Ah-- ah-- ah-choo-
！啊——啊——啊——
.36 days without a customer
.36 天没有顾客
.So hungry-
.好饿-
!Mr. Krabs-
！先生。蟹蟹-
!A customer
！一位顾客
.No food-
.没有食物-
.Three days
.三天
.Hold on, me bucko-
.等等，我笨蛋-
.Food's on the way
.食物正在路上
?Hey, you got money, right
？嘿，你有钱，对吧
.Yeah-
。是的-
Spongebob, bring this man-
.some grub before he keels over
海绵宝宝，带上这个人——
.在他倒下之前吃点东西
.Here you go, sir-
.给你，先生-
?Oh, crabby patties, huh-
？哦，蟹肉饼，嗯-
.Finest under the sea-
.海底最好的-
.Yeah, yeah, sure-
.是的，是的，当然-
?But where's the pizazz
？但活力在哪里
?Huh-
？哈-
.Look at this place-
.看看这个地方-
?I mean, what is the theme here
？我的意思是，这里的主题是什么
?Underwater
?水下
.It's boring
.很无聊
!Food
！食物
!Water
！水
!Atmosphere
！气氛
Nobody goes to a-
.restaurant for atmosphere
没有人去——
.气氛餐厅
!They go for food
！他们去寻找食物
!Hey, Tom-
！嘿，汤姆-
!Fred-
！弗雷德-
Hey, you want to eat
?at the Krusty Krab
嘿嘿，你想吃吗
？在蟹堡王
.Nah-
.不-
.Let's go to the Shell Shack
.我们去贝壳小屋吧
.They've got a talking dog
.他们有一只会说话的狗
.Great-
。伟大的-
?Say, what's a dog
？说，什么是狗
!Money walking-
！钱走路-
I need to think of
a gimmick like that
我需要想想
像那样的噱头
.to get people back in here
.让人们回到这里
.I have an idea-
.我有一个想法-
!Wait-
！等待-
!I've got an idea
！我有一个主意
And so, ladies and
gentlemen, make
所以，女士们，
先生们，让
sure you buy lots of crabby
.patties as I bury myself alive
你肯定买了很多螃蟹
.当我活埋自己时吃肉饼
[CHEERING]
[欢呼]
.No free refills
.没有免费续杯
!Hey, everyone-
！嘿，大家——
!Listen
！听
The talking dog at the
!Shell Shack is singing
会说话的狗
！贝壳小屋在唱歌
!Come on
！快点
.Mr. Krabs, I have an idea-
。先生。蟹蟹们，我有一个主意——
?What am I gonna do-
？我要做什么-
,If I don't find an idea
.I'll go out of business
,如果我找不到主意
.我会破产
.Mr. Krabs, I have an idea-
。先生。蟹蟹们，我有一个主意——
Why can't someone-
?give me an idea
为什么有人不能——
？给我一个主意
.Mr. Krabs, I have an idea-
。先生。蟹蟹们，我有一个主意——
Great Neptune in-
!heaven, I need an idea
伟大的海王星在-
！天哪，我需要一个主意
!Mr. Krabs-
！先生。蟹蟹-
.I have an idea
.我有一个主意
What in the name of money-
?are you waiting for, boy
以金钱的名义做什么——
？你在等吗，男孩
.Tell me
。告诉我
,OK, Mr. Krabs-
.prepare yourself
，好的，蟹老板-
.做好准备
Don't bother sitting
down because you'll
不用费心坐着
下来，因为你会
.just stand up when you see this
.看到这个就站起来
!Ta-da
！田田
!Great barrier reef-
!大堡礁-
!That patty's spoiled
！那个肉饼坏了
!Ba-ha-
！巴哈-
Mr. Krabs, it's
.not tainted meat
蟹老板，是
.没有受污染的肉
!It's painted meat
！是彩绘肉
Pretty patties, available
!in six designer colours
漂亮的肉饼，可以买到
!六种设计师颜色
.CHUCKLING] Mr]--
.Squidward, come look
.咯咯笑]先生]--
.章鱼哥，过来看看
?Don't that look appetising
？看起来是不是很有食欲呢？
.Mm mm good, sir-
.嗯嗯很好，先生-
Wait, give me an orange-
!patty with extra purple
等等，给我一个橙子——
！带有额外紫色的肉饼
?What's next
？下一步是什么
?Sequined milkshakes
?亮片奶昔
?Bow tie french fries-
?领结炸薯条-
.No-
。不-
!Pretty patties-
！漂亮的肉饼-
!Pretty patties
！漂亮的肉饼
!Stop it-
！别说了——
.I know this is a good idea
.我知道这是个好主意
.I'll show you
.我会告诉你
I'll-- I'll-- I'll
.open my own restaurant
我会-我会-我会
.开我自己的餐厅
!You'll see
！你会看到
?Hey Patrick, are you angry too
？嘿帕特里克，你也生气了吗
.Yeah-
。是的-
?What's the matter-
？怎么了-
.I can't see my forehead-
.我看不到我的额头-
?What's your problem
?你有什么问题
I have a good idea, and-
.no one else thinks so
我有一个好主意，而且——
.没有人这么认为
.Me too-
。我也是-
.Inflatable pants
.充气裤
?What's your idea
?你有什么想法
I'm gonna open up a restaurant-
.and sell pretty patties
我要开一家餐馆-
.并卖漂亮的肉饼
.Forget my dumb idea-
.忘记我愚蠢的想法-
!That's great
！那太棒了
Are you ready for-
?the big rush, Patrick
你准备好了吗——
？大冲刺，帕特里克
Pretty soon those
hungry customers
很快那些
饥饿的顾客
,will be lining up
.because we are open
,将会排队
.因为我们是开放的
.I'm ready
.我准备好了
!I'm ready
！我准备好了
[SNORING]
[打鼾]
Patrick, how long have
?we been sitting here
帕特里克，多久了
？我们一直坐在这里
Aw, I gotta draw a-
.new battery for this
噢，我得画一个——
.新电池
?What if Mr. Krabs was right-
？如果蟹老板是对的呢——
.Maybe my idea is dumb
.也许我的想法很愚蠢
Spongebob, sometimes we have-
to go deep inside ourselves
海绵宝宝，有时我们有——
深入我们自己的内心
.to solve our problems
.解决我们的问题
.I'm scared-
。我很害怕-
.Then I'm going in for you-
.那我就进去找你-
.Sorry
。对不起
.Stupid inflatable pants
.傻瓜充气裤
?Did you find anything-
？你有发现什么吗-
?Huh-
？哈-
?Hey, do you sell food here-
？嘿，你们这里卖食物吗-
.Yes, sir-
.是的，先生-
.We sell pretty patties
.我们卖漂亮的肉饼
.That thing's green-
.那个东西是绿色的-
!Green
！绿色的
[LAUGHING]
[笑]
!Mr. Krabs was right-
！先生。蟹老板说得对——
What am I gonna
?do with all these
我要做什么
？处理所有这些
?Hey, is that one purple-
？嘿，那是紫色的吗-
.Purple is my favourite colour
.紫色是我最喜欢的颜色
.This isn't half bad
.这还不错
Hey, world, pretty patties
!is the best idea ever
嘿，世界，漂亮的馅饼
！是有史以来最好的主意
:(FEMALE SPEAKER (ON TV
?Oh, Rick, how could you
:(女发言人（在电视上
？哦，瑞克，你怎么可以
.You and I, together we were one
.你和我，我们是一体的
MALE SPEAKER (ON
.TV): That was before
男发言者（上
.TV）：那是之前
.But now, I'm splitting us up
.但现在，我要分开我们
REPORTER: We interrupt
this programme
记者：我们打断一下
这个程序
for an important
.news announcement
对于一个重要的
.新闻公告
This wild throng
behind me is screaming
这狂野的人群
我身后在尖叫
for Bikini Bottom's
.newest culinary sensation
比基尼泳裤
.最新的烹饪感觉
.Let's take a listen
.我们来听听
!CROWD: Pretty patties
!CROWD: 漂亮的肉饼
!Pretty patties
！漂亮的肉饼
?Pretty patties-
?漂亮的肉饼-
REPORTER: It's easy to see that
.pretty patties are popular
记者：很容易看出
.漂亮的肉饼很受欢迎
But just what is
it about them that
但到底是什么
关于他们
drives Bikini
?Bottom feeders wild
驾驶比基尼
?底部饲养者野生
.ALL: They match our purses
.ALL：它们与我们的钱包相匹配
.They remind me of home-
.它们让我想起了家-
!Pretty patties rule-
！漂亮的肉饼占统治地位-
.REPORTER: Mr
Squarepants, how do
.记者：先生
方子，怎么办
?you explain all this success
？你解释了这一切的成功
--Uh-
--呃-
.I don't know
。我不知道
How can you make money-
?with such a stupid idea
怎么才能赚钱呢——
？有这么愚蠢的想法
REPORTER: And how
can you not make
记者：以及如何
你能不能做
money with such
?a brilliant idea
钱与这样的
？一个绝妙的主意
At first, we didn't know-
.what to do with all the money
起初，我们并不知道——
.如何处理所有的钱
,We tried burying it
.shredding it, and burning it
,我们试着把它埋起来
.粉碎它，然后燃烧它
But in the end, we decided
.to just give it all away
但最后我们决定
.把一切都放弃
.Come again, sir-
.再来吧，先生-
.I'm getting back in line-
.我要回去排队了-
!I don't believe it-
！我不相信-
!I've got to see this for myself
！我必须亲眼看看这个
.Hey, watch it, buddy-
.嘿，注意点，伙计-
I don't care how much you
.want your pretty patty
我不在乎你有多少
.想要你漂亮的小馅饼
You're going to have wait
.in line like the rest of us
你要等一下
.像我们其他人一样排队
.I never had a line-
.我从来没有台词-
?Who's number 46,853-
？46,853是谁的号码-
[CHEERING]
[欢呼]
.I never had 46,853 customers-
.我从来没有46,853个顾客-
.Here you go, sir-
.给你，先生-
.You stay pretty
.你保持美丽
.All right
。好的
?Mr. Krabs, is that you
？先生。蟹蟹，是你吗
?Isn't this great, Mr. Krabs
？这不是很棒吗，蟹老板
The pretty patties
.are a big hit
漂亮的肉饼
.很受欢迎
.They sure are, boy-
.他们确实是，男孩-
You're doing pretty
.well for yourself
你做得很好
.为你自己好
I guess you've completely
.forgotten the Krusty Krab
我猜你已经完全
.忘记了蟹堡王
.No sir, I haven't-
.不，先生，我没有-
In fact, sometimes I
really miss the old days
事实上，有时候我
真的很怀念以前的日子
.at the Krusty Krab
.在蟹堡王
I bet you miss Squidward and-
.the grill and the crow's nest
我打赌你想念章鱼哥而且——
.烤架和鸦巢
.Yeah, yeah-
。是啊是啊-
And you know what I miss
?the most, Mr. Krabs
你知道我想念什么
？最多，蟹老板先生
That tiny squeaky
sound you get when
那小小的吱吱声
当你听到的声音
.you rub two pickles together
.你把两个泡菜擦在一起
?You know what I mean, Mr. Krabs
？你知道我的意思，蟹老板
.Uh, yes-
.呃，是的-
.Yes, I do, lad
是的，我愿意，小伙子
Well, the Krusty Krab is
.only a short walk away
嗯，蟹堡王是
.仅几步之遥
Why don't you head on
?down for old time's sake
你为什么不继续前进
？为了旧时光而放下
.Oh, I can't leave, Mr. Krabs-
.哦，我不能离开，蟹老板-
?What about the stand
?展位怎么样
.Oh, don't worry, lad-
.哦，别担心，小伙子-
.I'll watch the stand for you
.我会为你看守看台
?You will-
？你会-
.No-
。不-
.I've got a better idea
.我有一个更好的主意
I'll take this old roadside
.stand off your hands for keeps
我会走这条旧路边
.保持双手远离
And in exchange, I'll
,give you the Krusty Krab
作为交换，我会
给你蟹堡王
,with Squidward, the grill
.and all those squeaky pickles
，和章鱼哥一起，烧烤
.还有那些吱吱作响的泡菜
?What did you say, Mr. Krabs-
？你说什么，蟹老板-
Here's the key-
这是关键——
.the Krusty Krab
.蟹堡王
.She's yours now
.她现在是你的了
.Thank you-
。谢谢-
?What should I do now, Mr. Krabs
？我现在该怎么办，蟹老板
.Run to her, boy-
.跑向她，男孩-
.She's waiting for you
.她在等你
I can't feel my-
.legs, Mr. Krabs
我感觉不到我的——
.legs，蟹老板
.Don't worry, lad-
.别担心，小伙子-
.I'll fix it
.我会解决它
Get this to the Krusty
.Krab on the double
把这个交给 Krusty
.双蟹蟹
!Good luck, lad
！祝你好运，小伙子
.Dreams do come true-
.梦想成真-
[GASP]
[喘气]
,Ladies and gentlemen-
Pretty Patties
,女士们先生们-
漂亮的肉饼
.is now under new management
.现在处于新的管理之下
?Who's next
?下一个是谁
[CHEERING]
[欢呼]
,I'm ready, I'm ready
.I'm ready for my money
，我准备好了，我准备好了
.我已经准备好拿我的钱了
.Welcome to Pretty Patties
.欢迎来到漂亮馅饼
?May I take your money
？我可以拿你的钱吗
.We want a refund, Krabs-
.我们想要退款，蟹蟹-
[AGREEMENT]
[协议]
?What-
？什么-
Your dumb pretty patties-
.turned my face purple
你那愚蠢的漂亮肉饼——
.把我的脸变成紫色
.Look what I got under my cape-
.看看我斗篷下有什么-
!And look at our tongues-
！看看我们的舌头——
?What's wrong with you-
？你这人怎么回事-
We want our money-
.back, all 46,853 of us
我们想要我们的钱——
.back，我们 46,853 人
?Hey, where'd he go
？嘿，他去哪儿了
!My key-
!我的钥匙-
?Where's my key
？我的钥匙在哪里
!Spongebob
！海绵宝宝
!Spongebob, let me in
！海绵宝宝，让我进去
!Spongebob
！海绵宝宝
[SQUEAKING]
[吱吱声]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[音乐播放]